<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Jamel Dargan</title>
    <link>https://jammy-bot.github.io/ds-portfolio/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Jamel Dargan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>

	<atom:link href="https://jammy-bot.github.io/ds-portfolio/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


    <item>
      <title>Online News Prediction</title>
      <link>https://jammy-bot.github.io/ds-portfolio/projects/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:04 -0500</pubDate>

      <guid>https://jammy-bot.github.io/ds-portfolio/projects/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Binary classification using sklearn pipeline, sequential feature selection, multiple algorithm comparison, hyperperameter tuning, and XGBoost | Objectives Through this project, I explore the following question:
 What features are best able to predict how often an online article will be shared?  Data Set This dataset was acquired from the University of California, Irvine&amp;rsquo;s Center for Machine Learning and Intelligent Systems archive (https://archive.ics.uci.edu/ml/datasets/Online+News+Popularity#).
 Data references articles published by Mashable (www.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Success at the Movies</title>
      <link>https://jammy-bot.github.io/ds-portfolio/projects/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:03 -0500</pubDate>

      <guid>https://jammy-bot.github.io/ds-portfolio/projects/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Multiple linear regression, SQLite3, PandaSQL | Introduction This project focuses on using data concerning recently successful movie titles. The goal is analysis helpful to the launch of a new studio.
Objectives This project explores the following questions and why:
 What are the recent top titles, by gross earnings? Which are the top performing studios? How fluid are their rankings What are the most frequently produced genres? &amp;hellip;The biggest earning? What is the genre mix for top studios?</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Pneumonia X-ray</title>
      <weight>5</weight>
      <link>https://jammy-bot.github.io/ds-portfolio/projects/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:02 -0500</pubDate>

      <guid>https://jammy-bot.github.io/ds-portfolio/projects/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Binary classification using sklearn pipeline, sequential feature selection, multiple algorithm comparison, hyperperameter tuning, and XGBoost | Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Pytorch Influence Functions</title>
      <weight>1</weight>
      <link>https://jammy-bot.github.io/ds-portfolio/projects/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:00:01 -0500</pubDate>

      <guid>https://jammy-bot.github.io/ds-portfolio/projects/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Using PyTorch to Identify Model Influences This project explores a machine learning package designed to identify which training data exert the most influence over a neural network models outcomes. It is based on the nimarb reimplementation of Influence Functions from the ICML2017 best paper: Understanding Black-box Predictions via Influence Functions by Pang Wei Koh and Percy Liang. The reference implementation can be found here: link.
The Dataset The project makes use of the CIFAR-10 image dataset, which consists of 50000 training images and 10000 test images in 10 classes.</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
